Contact

ruby200917@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/gaojz (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Triage Nursing
Emergency Nursing
Critical Care Nursing

Certifications

Basic Life Support (BLS)

Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS)

Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS)

AACN-Critical Care Registered Nurse CCRN- Adult

JingZhe "Ruby" Gao

BSN, RN, CCRN

Washington D.C. Metro Area

Summary

Experienced Intensive Care Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS), Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), BLS, Triage Nursing, and Critical Care Nursing.

Experience

Sibley Memorial Hospital, Johns Hopkins Medicine ICU RN, BSN, CCRN- Adult January 2019 - Present (1 year 6 months)
Washington D.C. Metro Area

Beijing United Family Hospital Emergency Room and ICU Registered Nurse August 2012 - December 2017 (5 years 5 months) Beijing City, China

• Emergency Room and ICU Nurse (Level 3 RN)

September 2016 - December 2017

- o Performed triage in a trauma certified emergency department in a Joint Commission International (JCI) accredited hospital.
- o Performed post-op, surgical, cardio-thoracic, and ICU critical care.
- o Provided cardio-vascular, respiratory, and neurological care.
- o Provided care to patients across the lifespan with different conditions from infants, children, pregnant women, and the elderly.
- o Assisted charge nurse in leadership, education, and supervisory duties.
- Emergency Room and ICU Nurse (Level 2 RN)

September 2014 - September 2016

- o Performed triage in a trauma certified emergency department.
- o Performed post-op, surgical, cardio-thoracic, and ICU critical care.
- o Performed cardio-vascular, respiratory, and neurological care.
- o Utilized Electronic Medical Record for patient charting.
- Emergency Room and ICU Nurse (Level 1 RN)

September 2013 – September 2014

- o Assisted senior nurses in critical care.
- o Performed non-critical patient care.
- New Graduate Program Resident (RN)
 August 2012 September 2013

Traditional Chinese Hospital of Beijing Dermatology Registered Nurse March 2012 - July 2012 (5 months) Beijing City, China

Armed Police Corps Hospital Nursing Intern June 2011 - March 2012 (10 months) Beijing City, China

Education

ChengDe Medical University
Associate's degree, Nursing · (2010 - 2012)

ChengDe Medical University
Bachelor of Science - BSN, Nursing · (2009 - 2012)

LangFang Health College
Associate's degree, Nursing · (2007 - 2010)